Guide to the William Singer Moorhead Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- MEMORABILIA, 1935-1988; Series IV; 13.0 linear feet (32 boxes)
  - Scrapbooks, 1966 January-1967 November 15 (Box 40, Folder 421-430)
  - Scrapbooks, 1967 November 16-1969 May 15 (Box 41, Folder 431-435)
  - Scrapbooks, 1969 May 17-September 15, 1969 September 17- 1970 May (Box 42, Folder 439-446)
  - Scrapbooks, 1970 June-1971 February 14, 1971 February 17- 1971 October (Box 43, Folder 447-455)
  - Scrapbooks, 1971 November-1972 October 20, 1972 October 22-December (Box 44, Folder 456-463)
  - Scrapbooks, 1973 January-October 17, 1973 October 19-1974 November 14 (Box 45, Folder 464-472)
  - Scrapbooks, 1974 November 17-1975 April 13, 1975 April 16-1976 December (Box 46, Folder 473-474)
  - Scrapbooks, 1977 January-1978 February 14 (Box 47, Folder 482-489)
  - Scrapbooks, 1978 February 15-June 15, 1978 June 17- 1979 October (Box 48, Folder 490-495)
  - Scrapbooks, 1979 November-1980 Dec, 1987, n. d. (Box 49, Folder 499-503)
  - Moorhead, Lucy Galpin
    - Entertaining in Washington
      - Published copy, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 504)
      - Correspondence, reviews, 1977-1979 (Box 50, Folder 505)
    - Party planning book, notes, 1959-1986 (Box 50, Folder 506-509)
  - Oversize
    - Awards, certificates, honorary degrees, 1958-1981 (Box 51, Folder 510)
    - Campaign memorabilia, n. d. (Box 51, Folder 511)
    - Campaign posters, 1958-1962, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 512)
    - Plaque with key of the William S. Moorhead Federal Building, Pittsburgh, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 513)
    - Photographs, 1940-1945, 1959, 1967-1974 (Box 52, Folder 514)
    - Scrapbook, 1958-1966 (Box 52, Folder 515)
    - Quiver of arrows and bow presented by D Corps Advisory Group, Pleiku, Vietnam, 1965 December 7 (Box 53)
    - Posters, 1975, undated (Box 54)
- National Endowment for the Humanities correspondence, 1964-1965; Accession 2016-M-059
  This accession comprises correspondence with government officials and others regarding Moorhead's interest in the establishment of the National Endowment for the Humanities, including soliciting support for federal legistalure for the needed funding. Some academic correspondents include faculty from Alfred University, Princeton University, Cornell University, University of Indiana, University of California, Tulane University, and California Institute of Technology. Other organizations include the New York Times, the John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, the American Association for the Advancement of Science, and the Association of Research Libraries.
  - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)